atomidata.com 2014-04-30

# Privacy Statement | Atomidata

Your privacy is important to atomidata.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that atomidata.com collects, and the ways in which atomidata.com uses that personal information. 

## Personal information collection

atomidata.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: 

  * information about your use of this website (standard log entries on our servers store your IP address, browser software details, and visited URLs);
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website's newsletter (including your email address); and
  * any information that you send to atomidata.com via the contact form on this site.

## Using personal information

atomidata.com may use your personal information to: 

  * respond to any questions or requests from your side
  * send you updates on recent events, services and products if you have subscribed to our newsletter

atomidata.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. 

## Securing your data

atomidata.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

atomidata.com will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. 

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that atomidata.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which atomidata.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information. 

## Updating this statement

atomidata.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. 

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. atomidata.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party. 

## Contact atomidata.com

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or atomidata.com's treatment of your personal information, please write to: 

  * by email to info@atomidata.com; or
  * by post to Atomidata, 11 Oktomvri 30/1, 1000 Skopje, Macedonia.
